A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1993.
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1993., Extent: 13 cubic feet (13 boxes). (Box 1-13)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Air Pollution Control, Dept. of - Clean Air Act, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Bottle Bill, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Board, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Earth Day, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Environment, Council on the (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Environment, Council on the (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Environmental Quality, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Environmental Quality, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: General (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: General (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Kim-Stan Landfill, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: King and Queen County Landfill, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Lake Gaston, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Landfills, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Marine Resource Commission, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Medical Waste Incinerator, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Recycling, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: State Water Control Board, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Swan hunting, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Virginia Wildlife Federation, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Virginia Museum of Natural History, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Alcohol and Drug Abuse, Govenor's Council on, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Alcohol Safety Action Program, Virginia, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Confederate flag, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Correctional Education, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (1 of 6), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (2 of 6), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (3 of 6), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (4 of 6), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (5 of 6), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (6 f 6), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of - Lyndon LaRouche (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of - Lyndon LaRouche (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Crime and Drugs, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Drunk driving, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Emergency Services, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Emergency Services, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: General (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: General (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: General (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Gun Control, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Radar detectors, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Violent Crime Initiative (1 of 5), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Violent Crime Initiative (2 of 5), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Violent Crime Initiative (3 of 5), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Violent Crime Initiative (4 of 5), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Violent Crime Initiative (5 of 5), 1993. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia Parole Board (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia Parole Board (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police (1 of 7), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police (2 of 7), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police (3 of 7), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police (4 of 7), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police (5 of 7), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police (6 of 7), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Virginia State Police (7 of 7), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Youth and Family Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Adopt A Highway Project, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Aviation, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Aviation, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Bypasses, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Coleman Bridge, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Corridor H Project, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Dept. of Motor Vehicles - DMV closings, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Dept. of Motor Vehicles - Driving privileges, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Dept. of Motor Vehicles - License plates, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Dept. of Motor Vehicles (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Dept. of Motor Vehicles (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Dept. of Motor Vehicles (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Federal Surface Transportation Act, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Transportation: General (1 of 8), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Transportation: General (2 of 8), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Transportation: General (3 of 8), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Transportation: General (4 of 8), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Transportation: General (5 of 8), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Transportation: General (6 of 8), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Transportation: General (7 of 8), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Transportation: General (8 of 8), 1993. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Transportation: HOV Lanes, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Rail, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Rest Areas, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Right of Way Project, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Roads, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Route 29, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Route 58, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Routes, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Seat belts, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Toll roads, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Transportation: Traffic lights, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Series II. Governor's Office, 1993., Extent: 11 cubic feet (11 boxes). (Box 14-24)
  Governor's Office correspondence, 1993, is housed in 11 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by topic. This series includes correspondence received by the Governor's Office that was answered by Governor Wilder or a member of his staff. Includes original letter, Response Referral Form, and attached response. Correspondence includes form letters, greetings, mass mailings, messages, appointment letters, congratulatory letters, resignation letters, sympathy letters, and thank you letters, as well as correspondence with various government officials and elected representatives, and correspondence from habitual writers.
  - Anniversary congratulations (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary congratulations (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Birthday greetings (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Birthday greetings (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Boards - Appointments (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Boards - Appointments (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Boards - Appointments (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Boards - Appointments (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Boards - Appointments, Interest (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Boards - Appointments, Interest (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Boards - Appointments, New Terms (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Boards - Appointments, New Terms (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Boards - Appointments, Recommendations (1 of 8), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Boards - Appointments, Recommendations (2 of 8), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Boards - Appointments, Recommendations (3 of 8), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Boards - Appointments, Recommendations (4 of 8), 1993. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Boards - Appointments, Recommendations (5 of 8), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Boards - Appointments, Recommendations (6 of 8), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Boards - Appointments, Recommendations (7 of 8), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Boards - Appointments, Recommendations (8 of 8), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Boards - Appointments, End of Term, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Boards - Appointments, Reappointments (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Boards - Appointments, Reappointments (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Boards - Appointments, Reappointments (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Boards - Appointments, Resignations, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Chain letters, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Circuit Court of Appeals, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - City Council, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Class reunions, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Congratulations (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Congratulations (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Congratulations (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Congratulations (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Constituent Affairs (1 of 8), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Constituent Affairs (2 of 8), 1993. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Constituent Affairs (3 of 8), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Affairs (4 of 8), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Affairs (5 of 8), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Affairs (6 of 8), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 3a)
  - Constituent Affairs (7 of 8), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 3b)
  - Constituent Affairs (8 of 8), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 3c)
  - Constituent Affairs - Requests (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Affairs - Requests (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Council of State Government, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Court of Appeals, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Governor's Association, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Deputy Chief of Staff Jorman Granger, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - District Court of Appeals, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Donation requests, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Drug Policy, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Eagle Scouts - Congratulations (1 of 6), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Eagle Scouts - Congratulations (2 of 6), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Eagle Scouts - Congratulations (3 of 6), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Eagle Scouts - Congratulations (4 of 6), 1993. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Eagle Scouts - Congratulations (5 of 6), 1993. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Eagle Scouts - Congratulations (6 of 6), 1993. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 4-H Program - Congratulations, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 4a)
  - Family Reunions - Congratulations/Welcome, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 4b)
  - Flag requests (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 17, Folder 4c)
  - Flag requests (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 17, Folder 4d)
  - Form Letters: Cat Licensing Bill (SB 728), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Form Letters: Educably Mentally Retarded, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Form Letters: Homes for Adults, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Form Letters: Jim Lavendar's Traveling Show (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Form Letters: Jim Lavendar's Traveling Show (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Form Letters: Lead-Based Paint Hazard Reduction Grant Program, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Form Letters: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of - Comprehensive Plan, 1994-2000 (1 of 7), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Form Letters: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of - Comprehensive Plan, 1994-2000 (2 of 7), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Form Letters: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of - Comprehensive Plan, 1994-2000 (3 of 7), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Form Letters: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of - Comprehensive Plan, 1994-2000 (4 of 7), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Form Letters: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of - Comprehensive Plan, 1994-2000 (5 of 7), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Form Letters: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of - Comprehensive Plan, 1994-2000 (6 of 7), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Form Letters: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of - Comprehensive Plan, 1994-2000 (7 of 7), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Form Letters: National Day of Prayer, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Form Letters: Night Time Chasing of Black Bears (HB 1751) (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Form Letters: Night Time Chasing of Bears (HB 1751) (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Form Letters: Night Time Chasing of Bears (HB 1751) (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Form Letters: Portmouth City Council - Amendment, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Form Letters: Preschool Education, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Form Letters: Richmond City Council Term, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Form Letters: Teacher Salaries, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Form Letters: Teenage Pregnancy, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Form Letters: Title Insurance Price Fixing (HB 2147), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Form Letters: Violent Crime Initiative (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Form Letters: Violent Crime Initiative (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Form Letters: Violent Crime Initiative (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Form Letters: Violent Crime Initiative (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Form Letters: Worker's Compensation (SB 908) (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Form Letters: Worker's Compensation (SB 908) (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Form Letters: Worker's Compensation (SB 908) (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Form Letters: Worker's Compensation (SB 908) (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Friendship Force, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Get Well, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Girl Scouts Gold Award - Congratulations, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Govenor's Correspondence: Ambassadors, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Govenor's Correspondence: Attorney General, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Govenor's Correspondence: General, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Govenor's Correspondence: General, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Govenor's Correspondence: Governors of other states, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Govenor's Correspondence: Governor's Fellowship Program, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Governor's Correspondence: House of Delegates, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Governor's Correspondence: House of Representative, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Governor's Correspondence: Mayors, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Governor's Correspondence: Personal friends, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Governor's Correspondence: President Clinton, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Governor's Correspondence: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Governor's Correspondence: Senate, Virginia, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Governor's Correspondence: Senator John Warren, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Governor's Correspondence: Virginia Congressional Delegation, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Habitual Writers: Berg, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Habitual Writers: Blackshear, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Habitual Writers: Blackwll, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Habitual Writers: Buch, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Habitual Writers: Collier, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Habitual Writers: Diamond, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Habitual Writers: Domossy, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Habitual Writers: Epperson, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Habitual Writers: Fishburne, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Habitual Writers: Friedman, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Habitual Writers: Gooding, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Habitual Writers: Gorham, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Habitual Writers: Hammett, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Habitual Writers: Hawkins, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Habitual Writers: Hughes, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Habitual Writers: Jafari, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Habitual Writers: Lewis, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Habitual Writers: Perry, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Habitual Writers: Puckett, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Habitual Writers: Radcliffe, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Habitual Writers: Smith, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Habitual Writers: Whiting, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Homosexual Marriage (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Homosexual Marriage (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Homosexual Marriage (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Homosexual Movement, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Community Council, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Services, Division of, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Letters from the Governor (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Letters from Governor (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - [Executive] Mansion, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - McFarlane, Walter, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Memorandums, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Messages from the Governor (1 of 7), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Messages from the Governor (2 of 7), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Messages from the Governor (3 of 7), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Messages from the Governor (4 of 7), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Messages from the Governor (5 of 7), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Messages from the Governor (6 of 7), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Messages from the Governor (7 of 7), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous/Campaign, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - National Governors Association (NGA), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - National Rifle Association (NRA), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Articles/Clippings, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - No Authority - Federal (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - No Authority - Federal (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - No Authority - Federal (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - No Authority - Legal (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - No Authority - Legal (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - No Authority - Local, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - No Authority - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Open House (1 of 3), 1993 Jan-June. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Open House (2 of 3), 1993 Jan-June. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Open House (3 of 3), 1993 Jan-June. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Parental Notification/Consent [on Abortion] (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Parental Notification/Consent [on Abortion] (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Policy Office, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Postcard File, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Press Office - Davidson, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Press Office - Katz, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Proclamations, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 11a)
  - Recommendations, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Requests, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Requests - Bios and Photos, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Resignations, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Resumes, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Retirement Requests (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Retirement Requests (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Scheduling Office - Cornish, Lyn, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Administration, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Finance, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Public Safety, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Transportation, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Senate Clerk's Office, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Senate/House Bills, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - State Corporation Commission (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - State Corporation Commission (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - State Corporation Commission (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - State Corporation Commission (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - State Employee Letters, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - State Lottery Dept., 1993. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - State Opinion Ballot, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Supreme Court of Virginia, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Sympathy (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Sympathy (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Sympathy/Thank You, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Thank You Letters from the Governor (1 of 5), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Thank You Letters from the Governor (2 of 5), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Thank You Letters from the Governor (3 of 5), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Thank You Letters from the Governor (4 of 5), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Thank You Letters from the Governor (5 of 5), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Thank You Letters to the Governor (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Thank You Letters to the Governor (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Thank You Letters to the Governor (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Virginia - Bottoms v. Bottoms Ruling (1 of 8), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Virginia - Bottoms v. Bottoms Ruling (2 of 8), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Virginia - Bottoms v. Bottoms Ruling (3 of 8), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Virginia - Bottoms v. Bottoms Ruling (4 of 8), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 8)